ikimap.com 2018-12-16

# Privacy policy | ikiMap

## Privacy policy of ikiMap

Out privacy policy describes how we gather, store or use the information that we collectthrough the different services or pages available on this site. It is important that you understand what information we collect and how we use, because the access to this site means that you accept our privacy policy.

### Cookies

Access to this site may involve the use of cookies. Cookies are small amounts of information that are stored on the browser used for each userso that the server can remember certain information that may subsequently be used. This information allows identifying you as a specific user and allowing you to save your personal preferences, as well as technic information such as visits or pages you visit.Those users that do not wish to receive cookies or want to be informed before they are stored on your computer, can configure his/her browser to that effect.

Most browsers nowadays allow cookies management in 3 different ways:

  1. Cookies are never accepted.
  2. The browser asks the user whether to accept each cookie.
  3. Cookies are always accepted

The browser also can include the possibility of specifying better what cookies have to be accepted and what not in particular. In particular, the user can normally accept any of the following options: reject cookies from certain domains; reject cookies from third parties; accept cookies as non-persistent (deleted when the browser is closed); allows the server to create cookies for a different domain. Also, the browsers can also allow users to view and delete cookies individually.

You have more information about cookies in: <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cookie>.

### Web Beacons

This site may also contain web beacons (also known as web bugs). Web beacons are typically small images of a pixel by pixel, visibleor invisible placed within the source code of the web page of a site. Web beacons are used in a similar manner to cookies. Also, web beacons are often used to measure the traffic of users who visit a web page and make a pattern of users of a site.

You have more information about web beacons in: <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_bug>.

### Thirds

In some cases, we share information about the visitors of this site on an anonymous or aggregate with third parties such as advertisers, sponsors or auditors for the only purpose of improving our services. All these processing tasks will be regulated according to the law and respectall their rightsin the field of data protection according to the current regulation.

This site measures the traffic with different solutions that may use cookies or web beacons to analyze what happens on our pages. We currently use the following solutions for the measurement of traffic from this site. You can see more information about the privacy policy of each of the solutions used for this purpose:

  * Google (Analytics): <http://www.google.com/intl/en_ALL/privacypolicy.html>.

This site can also host its own advertising, from affiliate, or from advertising networks. This advertisement is shown through advertising servers that also use cookies to display advertising content related to users. Each of these advertising servers have its own privacy policy, which can be consultedon their own web pages.

Currently this site hosts advertising of:

  * Google Adsense: <http://www.google.com/intl/en_ALL/privacypolicy.html>.
